Alright, now memorize it.
好啦，現在就記住吧。
Show it to everybody.
展示給大家看。
Got it?
知道了？
Alright, give it back to me.
好吧，還給我。
Five of hearts.
五顆心。
Real magic does exist.
真正的魔法確實存在。
Wow, Joey, how do you do it?
哇，喬伊，你是怎麼做到的？
I can't tell you that.
我不能告訴你這一點。
Well...
嗯...
Uh, somebody's at the door on the ceiling.
呃，有人在天花板的門口。
Oh, that's our unbelievably loud upstairs neighbor.
哦，那是我們樓上的鄰居，聲音大得令人難以置信。
Yeah, he took up the carpets and now you can hear everything.
是的，他鋪上了地毯，現在你可以聽到一切。
Well, why don't you go up there and ask him to just, like,
好吧，你為什麼不去那裡讓他，例如，
step lightly, please?
請輕一點好嗎？
I have, like, five times, but the guy is so charming that I
我大概有五次了，但這傢伙太迷人了，我
go up there to yell and then I end up apologizing to him.
上去大喊大叫，然後我就跟他道歉了。
Oh, that is silly!
哦，那真是愚蠢！
I'll go up there, I'll tell him to keep it down.
我會去那裡，我會告訴他小聲一點。
Alright, be my guest.
好吧，做我的客人吧。
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧。
If you really want to know how I did it, I'll show you.
如果你真的想知道我是怎麼做到的，我會告訴你。
When you handed me back the card, what you didn't see was I
當你把卡片還給我的時候，你沒看到的是我
looked at it so fast it was invisible to the naked eye.
看的速度之快，肉眼根本看不見。
I just did it.
我剛剛做到了。
Just did it again.
剛剛又做了一次。
Here, I'll slow it down so you guys can see it.
在這裡，我將放慢速度，以便大家可以看到。
Ready?
準備好？
Oh, yeah, I love that.
哦，是的，我喜歡那個。
Yeah, look, I have a boyfriend out here and he did everything I
是的，看，我在這裡有一個男朋友，他做了我所做的一切
told him to do and I don't get it.
告訴他要這樣做，但我不明白。
You don't have to tell him to do it.
你不必告訴他要這樣做。
Oh, thank you.
哦，謝謝。
Your job's a joke, you're broke Your love life's D.O.A. It's
你的工作是個笑話，你破產了你的愛情生活是D.O.A.這是
like you're always stuck in second gear And when it hasn't been your
就像你總是被困在二檔而當它不是你的時候
day, you're weak And now you're here, but I'll be there for you
那天，你很虛弱，現在你在這裡，但我會在你身邊
When the rain starts to pour I'll be there for you Like I've
當雨開始傾盆而下時，我會像以前一樣在你身邊
been there before I'll be there for you I'll be there for you
我會在你身邊 我會在你身邊
All right.
好的。
Anybody got a length of rope about six feet long?
有人有一段大約六英尺長的繩子嗎？
A little noose at the end?
最後有一個小絞索嗎？
Honey, what's the matter?
親愛的，怎麼了？
I just saw Janice.
我剛剛看到珍妮絲。
Yeah, she was at Rockefeller Center skating with her husband.
是的，她和先生在洛克斐勒中心滑冰。
She looked so happy.
她看起來很高興。
I almost feel bad for whipping that kid's pretzel at them.
我差點因為用那孩子的椒鹽捲餅來鞭打他們而感到難過。
Man, I remember the first time I saw that girl Catherine after we
夥計，我記得我們第一次見到凱瑟琳那個女孩的時候
broke up.
分手了。
She was just walking with her friend Donna, just laughing and talking.
她只是和她的朋友唐娜一起散步，有說有笑。
God, it killed me.
天哪，它殺了我。
Yes, but you ended up having sex with both of them that afternoon.
是的，但那天下午你最終和他們兩個都發生了性關係。
Sorry.
對不起。
Any excuse to tell that story.
任何藉口都可以講這個故事。
Hey, Chandler, there's a party tomorrow.
嘿，錢德勒，明天有一個聚會。
You'll feel better then.
那時你會感覺好一點。
Oh, you know what?
哦，你知道嗎？
I'm going to be okay.
我會沒事的。
You don't have to throw a party for me.
你不必為我舉辦派對。
It's Joey's birthday.
今天是喬伊的生日。
Oh, well, then if anybody should have a party, it should be him.
哦，好吧，那麼如果有人應該舉辦派對的話，那就應該是他了。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦，是啊，是啊。
I can't believe she's still up there.
我不敢相信她還在上面。
Okay, well, he totally screwed up the punchline.
好吧，好吧，他完全搞砸了笑點。
You know, it's supposed to be...
你知道，這應該是...
How's that coffee coming, dear?
親愛的，咖啡怎麼樣？
Yeah, right away, Mr. Kaplan.
是的，馬上，卡普蘭先生。
I'm not supposed to drink coffee.
我不應該喝咖啡。
It makes me gassy.
這讓我氣喘籲籲。
I know.
我知道。
I'll bet you're thinking, what's an intelligent girl who wants to be in
我敢打賭你一定在想，一個聰明的女孩想要加入什麼樣的行列？
fashion doing making coffee?
時尚界在做咖啡嗎？
Huh?
啊？
You got me.
你抓住了我。
I don't think I haven't noticed your potential.
我不認為我沒有註意到你的潛力。
Well, I've got a project for you that's a lot more related to
嗯，我有一個專案給你，它與以下內容更相關
fashion.
時尚。
How does that sound?
聽起來怎麼樣？
Oh, that sounds great.
哦，聽起來不錯。
Come on over here, sweetheart.
過來這裡吧，親愛的。
Come on, come on.
來吧，來吧。
Thank you so much, Mr. Kaplan.
非常感謝您，卡普蘭先生。
Thank you so much.
太感謝了。
I need these hangers separated ASAP.
我需要盡快將這些衣架分開。
You're welcome.
不客氣。
Oh, God, I hate my job.
哦，上帝，我討厭我的工作。
I hate it.
我恨它。
I hate my job.
我討厭我的工作。
I hate it.
我恨它。
Oh, no, honey, I'm sorry.
哦，不，親愛的，我很抱歉。
Oh, I want to quit, but then I think I should stick it
哦，我想放棄，但後來我想我應該堅持下去
out.
出去。
Then I think, why would such a person stay in such a demeaning
然後我想，這樣的人為什麼要留在這樣的屈辱中？
job just because it's remotely related to the field they're interested in?
工作只是因為它與他們感興趣的領域有一定的關係？
Gee, I don't know, Rach.
哎呀，我不知道，瑞秋。
Order up.
訂購吧。
I got a yentl soup, a James Beans, and a Howdy-Ho the
我買了一份元湯、一塊詹姆斯豆和一份 Howdy-Ho
duty.
責任。
All right.
好的。
Come on.
快點。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I don't mind paying my dues.
我不介意支付我的會費。
You know, it's just, how much am I going to learn about fashion
你知道，只是，我要了解多少時尚知識
by walking Myra, the arthritic seamstress, to the bathroom?
步行患有關節炎的女裁縫邁拉去洗手間？
Hi.
你好。
Is my misery amusing to you?
我的痛苦對你來說有趣嗎？
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I was just, uh...
我只是，呃...
It's not funny.
這不好笑。
This is actually my job.
這實際上是我的工作。
No, believe me.
不，相信我。
I've been there.
我去過那裡。
I had to sort mannequin heads at Mannequins Plus.
我必須在 Mannequins Plus 上對人體模型頭部進行分類。
Oh.
哦。
Well, then.
好吧，那麼。
So I'm just going to go back to talking to my friend here.
所以我要回去和我的朋友談談。
You can go back to enjoying your little hamburger.
你可以回去享用你的小漢堡了。
Actually, that's a Barbara Streisandwich.
事實上，那是芭芭拉史翠珊。
What?
什麼？
I named that one.
我給那個命名了。
Uh, just one other thing.
呃，只是另一件事。
Yes?
是的？
I, uh...
我，呃…
I work at Bloomingdale's, and I might know of a job possibility if
我在布魯明代爾百貨公司工作，如果
you're interested.
你有興趣。
Do you want my pickle?
你想要我的泡菜嗎？
Hey, guys.
嘿，夥計們。
Hey, Gunther.
嘿，岡瑟。
Hi.
你好。
I mean, you're going out on a date with the noisy guy upstairs?
我是說，你要跟樓上那個吵鬧的傢伙出去約會嗎？
Well, he's very charming.
嗯，他很有魅力。
I know he's too charming, but if you two start going out, then
我知道他太迷人了，但是如果你們兩個開始出去的話
it's just going to make it so much harder for me to hate
這只會讓我更難去恨
him.
他。
Well, you're just going to have to try.
好吧，你只需要嘗試一下。
All right.
好的。
Joey, where are the jello shots?
喬伊，果凍子彈在哪裡？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Chandler was supposed to be passing them around.
錢德勒應該把它們傳遞出去。
Chandler!
錢德勒！
Hello, hello!
你好，你好！
I don't know.
我不知道。
Somebody's feeling better.
有人感覺好多了。
Stick out your tongue.
伸出你的舌頭。
Take off your shirt.
脫掉你的襯衫。
Oh, my.
哦，我的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
How many of these did you have?
這些你有多少？
These are pure vodka.
這些是純伏特加。
Yeah, jello just like Mom used to make.
是的，果凍就像媽媽以前做的那樣。
The most unbelievable thing happened to me today.
今天最令我難以置信的事情發生在我身上。
Hi.
你好。
So, I'm having lunch at Monica's, and this guy starts talking to me,
所以，我在莫妮卡家吃午飯，這個人開始跟我說話，
and it turns out he works for a buyer at Bloomingdale's, and there
事實證明他為布魯明代爾百貨公司的一位買手工作
happens to be an opening in his department.
碰巧他的部門有一個空缺。
So, I gave him my phone number, and he's going to call me
所以，我給了他我的電話號碼，他會打電話給我
this weekend to see if he can get me an interview.
這個週末看看他是否能給我面試機會。
Wow.
哇。
I know.
我知道。
What?
什麼？
So, this guy's helping you for no apparent reason?
那麼，這個人無緣無故地幫助你？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
And he's a total stranger?
而他卻是個完全陌生的人？
Yeah.
是的。
His name is, um, Mark Something.
他的名字是，嗯，Mark Something。
Huh.
呵呵。
Sounds like Mark Something wants to have some sex.
聽起來 Mark Something 想要做愛。
He's what?
他是什麼？
Oh, I'm just saying.
哦，我只是說說而已。
I mean, why else would he just, you know, swoop in out of
我的意思是，不然他為什麼要，你知道，突然從
nowhere for no reason?
無緣無故無處可去？
To be nice?
表現得友善嗎？
Hey, Joey, are men ever nice to strange women for no reason?
嘿，喬伊，男人會無緣無故地對陌生女人好嗎？
No, only for sex.
不，只是為了性。
Thank you.
謝謝。
So, did you, uh, did you tell Mark Something about me?
那麼，你有沒有告訴馬克一些關於我的事情？
I didn't have to because I was wearing my I Heart Ross sandwich
我不需要，因為我穿著我的 I Heart Ross 三明治
board and ringing my bell.
登機並按下我的門鈴。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Joey!
喬伊！
Hey!
嘿！
Okay.
好的。
How many of that girl are you seeing?
那個女孩你見過幾個？
How hammered are you, huh?
你被錘到什麼程度了啊？
These are Joey's sisters.
這些是喬伊的姊妹。
Hi, Joey's sisters.
嗨，喬伊的姊妹們。
Hey.
嘿。
What are we drinking over here?
我們在這裡喝什麼？
Oh, well, I have, um, vodka and cranberry juice.
哦，好吧，我有，嗯，伏特加和酸果蔓汁。
No kidding?
沒開玩笑吧？
That's the exact same drink I made myself right after I shot my
這和我開槍後自己泡的酒一模一樣
husband.
丈夫。
Wow.
哇。
Okay, I don't know how to talk to you.
好吧，我不知道怎麼跟你說話。
What you doing?
你在做什麼？
I'm taking my ex-girlfriend off my speed dialer.
我要把我的前女友從我的快速撥號器中刪除。
Aww.
哇。
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
It's a good thing.
這是一件好事。
Why must we dial so speedily anyway?
為什麼我們必須這麼快地撥號呢？
Why must we rush through life?
為什麼我們必須匆匆過完一生？
Why can't we savor the precious moments?
為什麼我們不能珍惜那些珍貴的時刻呢？
Those are some huge breasts.
那是一些巨大的乳房。
You have.
你有。
Hi.
你好。
Yeah.
是的。
So, um, I heard about this, uh, Mark guy that, uh, Rachel met
所以，嗯，我聽說了這個，呃，馬克蓋伊，呃，雷切爾遇到了
today.
今天。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Isn't that great?
那不是很好嗎？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
So, uh, yeah, pretty, pretty good.
所以，嗯，是的，非常非常好。
He sounds like a nice, good guy.
聽起來他是個很好的人。
He is, and he is so dreamy.
他是，而且他是如此的夢想。
I mean, you know what?
我的意思是，你知道嗎？
When he left, I actually used the phrase homina, homina, homina.
當他離開時，我實際上用了“霍米納，霍米納，霍米納”這個詞。
That's excellent.
那太好了。
So he's just a nice guy.
所以他只是一個好人。
Do you really think this Mark doesn't want anything in exchange for helping
你真的認為這個馬克不需要任何東西來換取幫助嗎
you?
你？
Well, I assume I'll have to take showers with him, but, you know,
好吧，我想我得和他一起洗澡，但是，你知道，
that's true of any job.
任何工作都是如此。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
How are you feeling?
你感覺怎麼樣？
Well, my apartment isn't there anymore because I drank it.
好吧，我的公寓已經不存在了，因為我喝了它。
Where'd you get to?
你去哪裡了？
We lost you after you opened up all the presents.
當你開啟所有禮物後我們就失去了你。
Yeah.
是的。
Yeah, I ended up in the storage room and not alone.
是的，我最終進了儲藏室，而且並不孤單。
No woohooing.
沒有嗚嗚聲。
Why?
為什麼？
What happened?
發生了什麼事？
I fooled around with Joey's sister.
我和喬伊的妹妹鬼混。
Well, that's not the worst part.
嗯，這還不是最糟的部分。
What is the worst part?
最糟糕的部分是什麼？
I can't remember which sister.
記不清是哪位姊妹了。
You see what men do?
你看到男人會做什麼嗎？
Don't tell me men are nice.
別告訴我男人都很好。
This is men.
這是男人。
Are you insane?
你瘋了嗎？
I mean, Joey's gonna kill you.
我是說，喬伊會殺了你。
He's actually going to kill you dead.
他真的會殺了你。
Okay.
好的。
You don't think I thought of that?
你以為我沒有想到這一點嗎？
How can you not know which one?
你怎麼會不知道是哪一個呢？
I mean, it's unbelievable.
我的意思是，這令人難以置信。
I mean, was it Gina?
我是說，是吉娜嗎？
Which one is Gina?
哪一位是吉娜？
The dark, big hair with the airplane earrings.
深色的大頭髮和飛機耳環。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
That's not Gina.
那不是吉娜。
That's Dina.
那是迪娜。
Oh.
哦。
You see?
你看？
You can't tell which is which either.
你也分不清哪個是哪個。
Blah.
廢話。
We didn't fool around with any of them.
我們沒有和他們任何一個人開玩笑。
Blah, blah.
巴拉，巴拉。
Veronica.
維羅妮卡。
Look, it's gotta be Veronica, the girl in the red skirt.
看，一定是維羅妮卡，那個穿紅裙子的女孩。
I definitely stuck my tongue down her throat.
我確實把舌頭伸進了她的喉嚨。
That was me.
那是我。
Look, when I've been drinking, sometimes I tend to get a little overly
聽著，當我喝酒的時候，有時我會變得有點過度
friendly, and I'm sorry.
友好，我很抱歉。
That's okay.
沒關係。
That's all right.
That's okay.
沒關係。
Can I talk to you for a second?
我可以和你談談嗎？
Hey, Joey.
嘿，喬伊。
Come on.
快點。
Why can't we talk in here?
為什麼我們不能在這裡說話？
We're witnesses.
我們是見證人。
I just got off the phone with my sister.
我剛剛和姐姐通了電話。
Which one?
哪一個？
Mary Angela.
瑪麗·安吉拉.
Yeah.
是的。
No.
不。
Which one is she again?
她又是哪一位呢？
Why don't you ask Chandler?
為什麼不去問錢德勒？
Because he's the one who fooled around with her.
因為他就是那個捉弄她的人。
She told me you said you could really fall for her.
她告訴我你說你真的會愛上她。
Now, is that true, or are you just getting over Janice by groping
現在，這是真的嗎，還是你只是透過摸索克服了賈妮斯
my sister?
我的姊妹？
It's gotta be the first one.
這一定是第一個
Really?
真的嗎？
That's great!
那太棒了！
You and my sister are sitting in a tree.
你和我妹妹坐在一棵樹上。
Yep, I'm in a tree.
是的，我在樹上。
Did he call?
他打電話來了嗎？
Did Mark call?
馬克打來電話了嗎？
No, honey, I'm sorry.
不，親愛的，對不起。
But the weekend's not over yet.
但週末還沒結束。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Is that David?
那是大衛嗎？
Guess they're back from their date.
猜猜他們約會回來了。
Music.
音樂。
Very nice.
很不錯。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
So, how are you?
你好嗎？
I am good.
我很好。
I finished my book.
我完成了我的書。
Oh, yeah?
哦，是嗎？
What's it about?
是關於什麼的？
I don't remember.
我不記得了。
Do you want to take a walk?
你想散步嗎？
Yeah, I do.
是的，我願意。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Dear Mary Angela, Hi.
親愛的瑪麗·安吉拉，你好。
How's it going?
怎麼樣了？
This is the hardest letter I've ever had to write.
這是我寫過的最難的一封信。
What the hell's the matter with you?
你到底怎麼了？
How do you think Joey's gonna react when he finds out you blew
你認為喬伊發現你出軌後會有什麼反應
off his sister with a letter?
寫一封信給他妹妹？
Well, that's the part where you tell him that I moved to France.
嗯，這就是你告訴他我搬到法國的部分。
When actually, I'll be in Cuba.
實際上，我會在古巴。
Look, look, you've got to do this yourself, okay, in person.
聽著，聽著，你必須親自做這件事，好吧，親自做。
At least you know her name.
至少你知道她的名字。
You just go to the house and you ask for Mary Angela, okay?
你只要去家裡找瑪麗·安琪拉，好嗎？
When whichever one she is comes to the door, you take her for
無論她是誰來到你家門口，你都會把她當成
a walk, you let her down easy.
散步時，你很容易讓她失望。
Okay.
好的。
What if Mary Angela comes to the door and I ask for Mary
如果瑪麗·安琪拉來到門口，我去找瑪麗怎麼辦？
Angela?
安吉拉？
We're in Cuba.
我們在古巴。
Joey, what, uh, what, um, what are you doing here?
喬伊，什麼，呃，什麼，嗯，你在這裡做什麼？
Waiting for my grandma to finish my laundry.
等待奶奶洗完衣服。
What about you?
你呢？
I'm, uh, I'm here to see Mary Angela.
我，呃，我是來見瑪麗·安吉拉的。
You are so the man.
你就是這樣的男人。
Now, look, listen, listen, you've got to be cool because my grandma doesn't
現在，看，聽，聽，你必須冷靜，因為我奶奶不
know about you two yet and you do not want to take her
還不瞭解你們兩個，但你不想帶走她
off.
離開。
She was like the sixth person to spit on Mussolini's hanging body.
她是第六個向墨索里尼懸掛的屍體吐口水的人。
Where are your parents?
你的父母在哪裡？
Oh, they're in Vermont buying cigarettes.
哦，他們在佛蒙特州買香煙。
Where's Mary Angela?
瑪麗·安吉拉在哪裡？
She's right in there.
她就在那裡。
It's Sunday night and he didn't call.
那是週日晚上，他沒有打電話。
Bummer.
真糟糕。
Yeah, right.
是的，對。
Look at you.
看看你。
You're practically giddy.
你幾乎頭暈了。
No, I'm genuinely sorry the Mark thing didn't work out.
不，我真的很抱歉馬克的事情沒有成功。
Look, Rach, I want only good things for you.
聽著，瑞秋，我只想給你好的東西。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Why don't you just call Mark?
為什麼不直接打電話給馬克呢？
I mean, who says you have to sit here and wait for him?
我是說，誰說你必須坐在這裡等他？
You've got to make stuff happen.
你必須讓事情發生。
But you don't want to seem too pushy.
但你不想顯得太咄咄逼人。
It's not pushy.
這並不咄咄逼人。
He gave her his home number.
他給了她他的家庭電話號碼。
What?
什麼？
He gave you his home number as in, like, to his home?
他給了你他家的電話號碼，例如，到他家？
Yeah, and you don't mind if I call because you only want good
是的，你不介意我打電話，因為你只想要好的
things for me.
為我準備的東西。
That's right.
這是正確的。
Good things.
好東西。
That is what I said.
我就是這麼說的。
Hello, Mark?
你好，馬克？
Hi, it's Rach.
嗨，我是瑞秋。
It's Rachel Green.
這是雷切爾·格林。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Don't you apologize.
你不用道歉。
Yeah, I'll call.
是的，我會打電話。
He left my number at work.
他在工作時留下了我的電話號碼。
He was going to get it, but he was helping his niece with
他本想得到它，但他正在幫助他的侄女
her report on the Pioneers.
她關於拓荒者隊的報告。
So made up.
於是就編好了。
Yeah, oh, my God.
是的，哦，天哪。
Tomorrow?
明天？
No, it's perfect.
不，它很完美。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
Thank you so much.
太感謝了。
Great.
偉大的。
Bye.
再見。
I got the interview.
我收到面試了
Oh, yay!
哦，耶！
There you go.
就這樣吧。
He even offered to meet me for lunch and prep me for it.
他甚至主動提出要和我一起吃午餐，並幫我做好準備。
Oh, that is amazing!
哦，太棒了！
Yeah, well, if I know Mark, and I think I do, I'd expect
是的，好吧，如果我認識馬克，而且我想我認識，我希望
nothing less.
一點也不遜色。
I got to figure out what I'm going to wear.
我得想好我要穿什麼。
High collar and baggy pants say I'm a pro.
高領和寬鬆的褲子表明我是專業人士。
Yeah, right.
是的，對。
Okay, I'll see you guys later.
好的，我們稍後見。
You go get them.
你去找他們。
What did I do to you?
我對你做了什麼？
Did I hurt you in some way?
我在某些方面傷害了你嗎？
Why don't you call him?
為什麼不打電話給他？
Well, thank you very much.
嗯，非常感謝。
You know, now he's going to prep her.
你知道，現在他要讓她做好準備。
You know, prep her as in what you do before you surgically remove
你知道，像手術切除之前一樣為她做好準備
the boyfriend.
男朋友。
Are you crazy?
你瘋了？
Oh, am I?
哦，我是嗎？
Am I?
我是嗎？
Am I out of my mind?
我瘋了嗎？
Am I losing my senses?
我失去理智了嗎？
This dreamy guy is taking my girlfriend out for a meal.
這個夢幻般的傢伙要帶我女朋友出去吃飯。
Ross, you know, this isn't even about you.
羅斯，你知道，這與你無關。
I mean, this is about Rachel and something wonderful happening for her.
我的意思是，這是關於瑞秋和她身上發生的一些奇妙的事情。
I mean, you know, even if you're right, what if he wants to
我的意思是，你知道，即使你是對的，如果他想要怎麼辦？
sleep with her?
和她一起睡嗎？
Does that mean he gets to?
這是否意味著他可以做到？
No, but...
不，但是…
I mean, don't you trust her?
我的意思是，你不信任她嗎？
Well, yeah.
嗯，是的。
Then get over yourself.
然後克服自己。
Grow up.
長大。
You grow up.
你長大了。
This tiramisu is excellent.
這個提拉米蘇很棒。
Did you make it, Mary Angela?
你成功了嗎，瑪麗·安吉拉？
No, I did.
不，我做到了。
It's yummy.
很好吃。
So, uh, Mary Angela, do you like it?
那麼，呃，瑪麗·安吉拉，你喜歡嗎？
Of course.
當然。
It's her favorite.
這是她的最愛。
So, um, Mary Angela, what's your second favorite?
那麼，嗯，瑪麗·安吉拉，你第二喜歡什麼？
More of Grandma's tiramisu.
更多奶奶的提拉米蘇。
Oh, would you just please give me the recipe because this is great.
哦，請給我食譜好嗎，因為這太棒了。
It's top notch.
這是一流的。
That guy is with me.
那個人和我在一起。
So am I.
我也是。
Excuse yourself and go to the bathroom.
對不起，去趟洗手間。
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
I was just squinting.
我只是瞇著眼。
That doesn't mean anything.
那沒有任何意義。
Just do it.
去做就對了。
Will you excuse me?
你能原諒我嗎？
I have to, um...
我必須，嗯...
Hey.
嘿。
Finally!
最後！
I thought we'd never be alone.
我以為我們永遠不會孤單。
Can I just tell you something?
我可以告訴你一件事嗎？
I have not stopped thinking about you since the party.
自從聚會之後我就一直想念你。
Look, I may have jumped the gun here.
聽著，我可能有點操之過急了。
Uh...
呃...
I just got out of a relationship and I'm not really in a...
我剛剛結束一段感情，而且我並沒有真正處於一段關係中......
in a commitment kind of place.
在一種承諾的地方。
So me neither.
所以我也不是。
God.
上帝。
Mary Angela was right.
瑪麗·安吉拉是對的。
You do have the softest lips.
你確實有最柔軟的嘴唇。
Oh.
哦。
You're not Mary Angela?
你不是瑪麗·安吉拉？
No.
不。
I'm married to Reese.
我和里斯結婚了。
This is so bad.
這太糟糕了。
If you're not Mary Angela, then who is?
如果你不是瑪麗·安吉拉，那誰是？
I am.
我是。
Oh, it's so bad.
噢，太糟糕了。
Joey!
喬伊！
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事？
You're it.
你就是它。
Now run and hide.
現在跑並躲起來。
It's no big deal.
沒什麼大不了的。
Chandler was just kissing me because he thought I was Mary Angela.
錢德勒只是在吻我，因為他以為我是瑪麗·安琪拉。
What?
什麼？
How could you do that?
你怎麼能這麼做？
How could you think she was Mary Angela?
你怎麼會認為她是瑪麗·安吉拉？
I wasn't sure which one Mary Angela was.
我不確定瑪麗·安吉拉是哪一位。
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
聽著，我很抱歉，好嗎？
I was really drunk and you guys all look really similar.
我真的喝醉了，你們看起來真的很像。
I say punch him, Joey.
我說打他，喬伊。
Yeah!
是的！
Punch him!
打他！
No, you know what?
不，你知道嗎？
We should all calm down because, you know, your brother's not gonna punch
我們都應該冷靜下來，因為你知道，你的兄弟不會打人
me.
我。
Yeah?
是的？
Well, that is usually what I would do, but I just never thought
嗯，這通常是我會做的，但我只是沒想到
you'd be on the receiving end of it.
你會成為它的接收端。
How could you do this?
你怎麼能這麼做？
Hey!
嘿！
Where'd everybody go?
大家都去哪了？
Hey, no, no.
嘿，不，不。
Why don't you go into the den?
為什麼不進書房呢？
I think cops is on.
我想警察已經出動了
Joey, if you want to punch me, go ahead.
喬伊，如果你想打我，就儘管吧。
I deserve it.
我應得的。
But I just want you to know that I would never soberly hurt
但我只是想讓你知道我永遠不會清醒地傷害
you or your family.
您或您的家人。
You're my best friend.
你是我最好的朋友。
And I would never do anything like this ever again.
我再也不會做這樣的事情了。
So what?
所以呢？
I say punch him!
我說打他！
Punch him!
打他！
I'm not gonna punch Chandler.
我不會打錢德勒。
I'll do it.
我會做的。
No, you won't.
不，你不會。
Look, he knows he did a terrible thing and I believe him.
看，他知道他做了一件可怕的事情，我相信他。
He's sorry.
他很抱歉。
But you got one more apology to make.
但你還得再道歉一次。
All right?
好的？
You got to apologize to Mary Angela.
你必須向瑪麗·安吉拉道歉。
Okay, absolutely.
好吧，絕對可以。
You got it.
你明白了。
All right.
好的。
Cookie, now you can punch.
餅乾，現在你可以打拳了。
What?
什麼？
Hey!
嘿！
Hi.
你好。
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼？
Uh, you know, this building's on my paper routes, so, uh...
呃，你知道，這棟建築在我的送紙路線上，所以，呃......
Hi.
你好。
How'd it go?
怎麼樣？
Oh, well, the woman I interviewed with was pretty tough, but, you know,
哦，好吧，我採訪的那個女人非常強硬，但是，你知道，
thank God Mark coached me, because once I started talking about the fall
感謝上帝馬克指導了我，因為一旦我開始談論秋天
line, she got all happy and wouldn't shut up.
線，她很高興，不肯閉嘴。
I'm so proud of you.
我為你感到驕傲。
Me too.
我也是。
Listen, I'm, uh...
聽著，我，呃...
I'm sorry I've been so crazy and jealous, and...
對不起，我如此瘋狂和嫉妒，而且...
It's just I like you a lot, so...
只是我太喜歡你了，所以…
I know.
我知道。
Yeah?
是的？
Yeah.
是的。
Rachel.
雷切爾。
Yeah.
是的。
Hi.
你好。
Hi, Mark.
嗨，馬克。
Hi.
你好。
Um, I just talked to Joanna and she loves you.
嗯，我剛剛和喬安娜談過，她愛你。
You got it.
你明白了。
You got the job.
你得到了這份工作。
I did?
我做到了？
Yes.
是的。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Congratulations!
恭喜！
Wow!
哇！
Lations, lations, lations.
關係，關係，關係。
So, uh, Phoebe.
所以，呃，菲比。
Hmm?
唔？
How was your date?
你的約會怎麼樣？
Oh, well, you know.
哦，好吧，你知道。
Yeah, I do know.
是的，我知道。
Ugh, you were eavesdropping?
呃，你偷聽了？
Eavesdropping.
竊聽。
Phoebs, the ceiling tiles were falling down.
菲布，天花板的磁磚掉下來了。
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦，對不起。
But I really like this guy and I think he really happens to
但我真的很喜歡這個人而且我認為他真的碰巧
like me.
像我這樣的。
Maybe he's just jumping on a pogo stick and he really likes it.
也許他只是在彈簧單高蹺上跳躍，而他真的很喜歡它。
Maybe the pogo stick likes it, too.
也許彈簧單高蹺也喜歡它。
All right, that's it.
好吧，就是這樣。
He cannot do this to Phoebe.
他不能這樣對待菲比。
This guy's gonna get the butt-kicking of a lifetime.
這傢伙會受到一輩子的鞭打。
But is he a big guy?
但他是個大人物嗎？
Uh, we'll all go.
呃，我們都走吧。
Come on.
快點。
Well, I'll say I just got beat up by a girl.
好吧，我會說我剛剛被一個女孩毆打了。
They need me.
他們需要我。
Thanks, you guys.
謝謝你們。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Don't worry.
不用擔心。
God.
上帝。
I hope they kick his ass.
我希望他們踢他的屁股。
Honey, I'm sorry.
親愛的，對不起。
You know, if it's any consolation, he really did sound like he was
你知道，如果有什麼安慰的話，他聽起來確實像
having more fun with you.
和你一起玩得更開心。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。